<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>iDeepLearn</title>
  
  <subtitle>Simple, Utility, Flexibility.</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/"/>
  <updated>2018-09-08T09:00:33.274Z</updated>
  <id>http://ideeplearn.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>DeepCreator</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Communication</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Communication.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Communication.html</id>
    <published>2018-09-08T08:09:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-09-08T09:00:33.274Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/7844471_orig.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Equality and respect, seeking common ground while reserving differences, cooperation and win-win, flexible response, and getting things done.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><strong>The moment to let someone shut up is to know your boundaries.</strong>  – DeepCreator</p><p>If you have something to say, do  well.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/COMMUNICATION-CIRCLE.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><h2 id="Effective-Communication"><a href="#Effective-Communication" class="headerlink" title="Effective Communication"></a><a href="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Effective Communication</a></h2><h3 id="INTRODUCTION"><a href="#INTRODUCTION" class="headerlink" title="INTRODUCTION"></a>INTRODUCTION</h3><p>We communicate with other people in almost every single second of our lives. We communicate to deliver a message to other people so that in return receiving a respond. Communication help us co-operate with people around us as well as understand them and share our thought. From the basis of daily family life to the busy working environment of school and workplace, we must practice how to communicate effectively to ensure that we are connecting with other. In this website, I am telling you everything to know about communication and how it can affect motivation.</p><h3 id="Good-amp-Bad-Communication"><a href="#Good-amp-Bad-Communication" class="headerlink" title="Good &amp; Bad Communication"></a>Good &amp; Bad Communication</h3><p>Understand the basics of<br>effective communication and how to overcome barriers.  </p><p>What is effective communication?<br>Effective communication is not only about conveying a message that you want to say. It  is about conveying the message so that other people understand and respond to it.</p><p>Effective communication between 2 parties requires sending and receiving message in both directions. The sender must be able to deliver their message to the receiver and the receiver must respond to the message in order to complete a cycle of communication. This will ensure a smooth flow of idea and understanding between both parties and prevent misunderstanding.</p><p>Communication happens everywhere from the basis of our daily family life to our working or learning environment. We interact with other people every single day in order to co-operate with them and work towards a common goal. That’s why effective communication is extremely important.</p><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/7844471.jpg?354" alt=""><br>Effective communication cycle</p><p>The Benefits of Effective Communication</p><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/5117431.jpg?166" alt=""><br>By practicing effective communication in our workplace, there are many benefits arises from it.</p><p>By communicating effectively, two parties can exchange information thoroughly with lesser possibility of misunderstanding or missing out on information. Thus, allow more accurate assess on the information and avoid any reduction in productivity.<br>Effective communication in workplace allows members to work together effectively without any worries about being shun do to their different background or hierarchy standing. Workers tend to do better when they are respected and be heard by others.<br>By practicing good communication, one would be able to build his self-esteem and be more confident when they have to speak and respond to other.<br>Most important of all, effective communication helps you build your relationships with other people. Through good communication, you are able to cooperate efficiently with others and thus, build stronger bond as you gain trust from others.</p><p>(Source: Effectivecommunicationadvice)</p><p>Barriers to effective communication<br><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/4834603.gif?213" alt=""></p><p>Ineffective communication can always occur and lead to communication breakdown as both parties fail to deliver or process the received message. Without constant sending and feedback in communication, the parties will not be able to understand and respond appropriately to the idea of the others and thus, cannot co-operate. Without good communication, there will be no teamwork in the workplace and there sure to be misunderstandings and conflict. The video below is a comical example of how language barrier in communication and assumptions might lead to a whole lot of misunderstanding.</p><p>Ineffective communication is seen as a problems cause by different ‘barriers’. Those barriers includes:</p><p>Physical distraction: The elements of the surrounding such as poor lighting, background noises, atmosphere, etc can really drive off your focus span during communication.</p><p>Attitude: If you feel strong emotions like angered or unhappy, you will most likely feel uncomfortable to listen or even speak with someone. This will not only halt the effectiveness of your communication but also make you less productive and co-operative. Emotions can also interfere with your confidence in facing others and thus, make you less of a dependable person in other’s eyes.</p><p>Channel barriers: How you channel your message is very important. For example: If you are trying to send instruction to someone, it would be more ideal to have it in written form rather than telling them verbally, or else it would be difficult to follow through. People who are unaware of how they should communicate could get in a lot of problem.</p><p>Stereotype: When you have stereotypical thoughts about someone base on their background and culture, it would be hard for you to communicate effectively as you won’t have enough trust in them. Holding stereotypical thoughts about someone else who simply put a barrier between you and them.</p><p>Language barrier: In communication, language barriers can happen anytime. Everyone have their own mother tongue language as well as their own interpretation of certain words and phrases. Thus, conflicting language might occur and the communicators might not be able to understand each other.  </p><p>Time barrier: Let say you complete a great design for a new car and you wanted to report it to your boss, when will it be better to tell him? Midnight right after you finish your design? or next morning when your boss is at work? Choosing when to approach a person to discuss something with them is very important because if you do not choose the appropriate time, the person whom you are trying to deliver the message to might not be interested in listening to you.</p><p>Structural problems in the organization: If the structure in an organization is unclear, then members of the organisation might have problems communicating as they don’t know who and when to communicate. New members should be instructed clearly  to prevent any communication mishap or confusion.  </p><p>Lack of knowledge on the subjects: Lack of understanding on the subject would make communication difficult for both the sender and the receiver. Usually, people communicate easier when the subject of matter is something that both of them are familiar with. If the sender is not sure about the matter he is communicating, then the receiver would be troubled in understanding as well.</p><p>Information overload: Processing information takes time and if communication does not goes at a pace where both parties can have enough time to carry out their thought process, then it will cause communication breakdown as concentration and interest might be haltered.</p><p>Assumptions: Assuming something without clarification is a very dangerous thing to do. When you assume the wrong information, it is very likely that you will make wrong decisions and conclusion. This could cause many extended problems and lead to conflicts as well.</p><p>(Source: Effectivecommunicationadvice / marin.edu / CTE)</p><p>How to overcome communication barriers?</p><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/5699859.jpg" alt=""></p><p>Communication barriers are not impossible to overcome at all. They can be avoided if you know how to deal with them correctly. Here are some advice for you to overcome these problems</p><p>Be attentive: of who you are communicating with. If they have trouble getting your message, you should know how to adjust your communication method in order to get through with them.</p><p>Be patience: is the key to effective communication. You must never rush anything and take your time in order to make communication work thoroughly between you can your partner</p><p>Never assume: because you could interpretative the foul information and carry out wrong decisions or responds. Always clarify something if you are unclear.</p><p>Be friendly and open-minded: towards others you are co-operating with. You must never judge others or let your feelings towards someone interfere with your work. Also, you must be emphatic towards other to work out the problem rather than just let things be. Workplace often encourage those who co-operate well with others no matter what.  </p><p>Be aware: of who you are communicating with and how you should communicate with them. This would help you approach that person and approach in a better manner and style and prevent and problems that might occur.</p><h3 id="Types-of-communication"><a href="#Types-of-communication" class="headerlink" title="Types of communication"></a>Types of communication</h3><p>Learn about the various way we use to communicate.</p><p>Types of communications<br>Nowadays, we are exposed to many form of communications such as:<br>All of these mentioned form of communication and many more can be classified into 2 different categories</p><ol><li>Verbal communication</li><li>Non-verbal communication<br>Verbal communication</li></ol><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/7681958.jpg?150" alt=""><br>Verbal communication is the type of communication that involved communicating verbally using language that the sender and the receiver understand.It is meant to be done so that the sender and the receiver are able to understand each other effectively. There are two types of verbal communication: Oral communication and written communication.</p><ul><li>Oral communication<br>Oral communication involve communicating orally via spoken words. Many examples of oral communication is face    to face talking, phone, radio, television and any forms of communication that deliver the message to the receiver’s ears. In oral communication, factors such as tone, speed, volume and confidence can affect its effectiveness.</li></ul><p>Oral communication is very convenience as it can be perform very quickly and it allows sender to receive feedback faster. The sender are also able to express their feelings through verbal communication and bring certain mood effect to the receiver. In face-to-face communication, the speaker can also observe the other person’s expression and decide how to respond accordingly. Verbal communication can become an useful way to motivate others if you have the right skill and confidence</p><p>However, oral communication can become unsuccessful if external factors are encountered such as loud noise background or physical disturbance which could interrupt speaking. Oral communication cannot be done with a person who is either deaf, mute or does not speak the same language.In face-to-face communication, the communicator have to think of what to say while interpret what they heard which could cause them confusion and fail to communicate wisely. This could be worsen if that person lack confidence or communication skill.</p><ul><li>Written communication<br>Written communication involve composing the message in a written format and deliver it via soft copy or hard copy.This type of communication can be seen with the use of fax, text messages, social network, e-mail, etc. Written communication is influence by the structure of the language such as grammar and vocabulary.</li></ul><p>Written communication is an important skill applied in the business environment. It is very important as it can be use to compose a lot of information together, save into many copies and deliver to many people at once.Written information can be recorded and stored for later study which can be useful to manage and organize detailed and mass information. The receiver will be able to understand the message more thoroughly as well.</p><p>However, written communication does not bring instant feedback like verbal communication do. It also requires good writing skill and time to compose the message and it could be a challenge to those who lack writing skill. Written communication allows people to compose more information and tend to lead to information overload.People who are blind are unable to communicate by writing.</p><p>(Source: Notes Desk)</p><p>Non-verbal communication</p><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/5264329.jpg" alt=""><br>Non-verbal communication refers to any other form of communication that does not involve writing, talking or use of words and languages. Body language such as posture, facial expression, hand movements, tone, etc are all consider non-verbal communication. It is a way of communicating messages or rather command without using words. The receiver will have to base on their own interpretation to understand the message and thus, the sender must be able to give clear signals. Non-verbal communication is very important as performing it effectively will decide how comfortable and attentive the other person feel about communicating with you.</p><p>Non verbal communication has 3 main elements:</p><p>Appearance: How the speaker appears will decide how interested the listeners will be. In a workplace, a person with professional look and confident appearance will surely catch the attention of many. External factor such as room light, temperature and noise level will also influence the appearance of a conversation</p><p>Body language: There are many things that accounted to body language include hand signals, posture and facial expressions. When combine well in verbal communication, these body language could help emphasize the effectiveness of delivering the message.</p><p>Sounds: Speaking fluently with good tone, clear voice and normal speed could help verbal communication a lot more effective.  </p><p>(Source: Notes Desk)</p><p>Visual communication<br><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/9058027.jpg?181" alt=""><br>It is always said that ‘a picture worth a thousand words’. Visual aids are always important in communication as it will act as an illustration for the receiver to understand the message a lot faster and easier. In business presentation, the presenter are often accompanied by powerpoint slides or videos to help them get the message across easily without having to say too much. Visual communication relies on the ability to interpret images by the audience. Thus, if we are not careful with the images we choose, we could easily make the audience interpret the wrong message. In our daily life, we could see visual communication everywhere in the public such as banners, signboards, traffic light, maps and etc. Traffic light gives command to vehicle users by flickering lights signalling the action they should take like red for stop and green for go.</p><p>(Source: Managementstudyguide)</p><p>Understand formal and informal communication</p><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/6702327.jpg?206" alt=""><br>Different type of communications are used depend on the situations. Certain form of communication can be useful and appropriate for certain use but it will not be consider ethical. For example: When a staff want to report to his boss, he will have to write a proper grammar using professional language and realistic data. He would be fired if he posted a note on his boss’ Facebook page because it is not professional and since Facebook is a social network place that is not very suitable for work discussion.</p><p> +Formal communication<br>Formal communication refers to appropriate and professional style of communication that is used in business workplace. A person who needs to communicate formally requires to follow standard rules and outlines set by the higher authority. In formal communication, correct grammar and pronunciation are required while slang and foul language should be avoided at all cost as we used it to communicate with our co-operatives and people of higher rank. Thus, professionalism and formalism always come first.</p><p> +Informal communication<br>Informal communication refers to a more free and comfortable style of communication as the communicator is allow to communicate in anyway they wish. In informal communication, there are no standard and limits to how one should use their language, thus, make it easier for communicator to communicate. In our daily life, we used informal communication with our friends and family as a more natural way of communication have people express themselves better and build better relationship. Thus, practicing informal communication in workplace to create a friendlier environment is not something wrong but should rather be done as long as it has a limit to it.</p><p>(Source: Notes Desk)</p><h3 id="Communication-in-business"><a href="#Communication-in-business" class="headerlink" title="Communication in business"></a>Communication in business</h3><p>Look into how communication flow in the business world.</p><p>Communication in business - How does it go?<br>To begin with, let’s go through some basic concepts about communication in business. A business is structured using a hierarchical structure where each member would have responsible over other member of lower rank. The purpose of this hierarchical structure is to maintain a firm order and rule within a business and ensure that everyone within the organisation co-operate and communicate effectively.There are two main types of organisational structure: Tall structure and flat structure. Let’s look at the graph below</p><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/4449028_orig.gif" alt=""><br>Diagram of tall and flat organisational structure<br>Organisation A is a tall organisational structure. In a tall structure, there are various levels of hierarchical ranking and thus, it has a long chain of command through the many layers from the highest (CEO) to lowest (employees). With the many layers, each manager will only have control over a limited number of employee, thus, they will have smaller span of control. Tall organisation structure is often applied in large companies where there are more members within the organisation itself.</p><p>Organisation B is a flat organisational structure. In a flat structure, there are lesser layers of hierarchical ranking and thus, make the chain of command shorter. Since there are lesser layers of authority, a manager would have more span of control since they will have to be in charge of more employees. Flat organisations are often embodied within small organisations owned by an individual sole trader where there are fewer employees.</p><p>By looking at the example of an organisational chart below, you would be able to understand how the hierarchical system work overall. The managing director sit on top and take charge of all the other directors while each directors take care of the team leaders who were assigned to keep an eye out for the teams. But, how do they communicate with each other?</p><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/4724169_orig.gif" alt=""><br>Example of an organisational chart<br>In a business organisation, communication goes in an order and not simply from one person to another. Communication in business is perform in a very mannered way. For examples, Production Team Members cannot simply report to the Managing Director who is on the top. They can only report to the Managing Director after they have reported to the Production Team Leaders who will report to the Operations Director to the Managing Director. This is known as Vertical Communication, communication between members of different ranks. On the other hand, communication between members of the same rank is know as Horizontal Communication. Communication between members is known as Internal Communication while communicating with people outside of the business organisation such as suppliers or customers are called External Communication. Within communication in a organization, vertical communication must be made very clear to everyone or else there will be a big communication breakdown between managers and employees. Vertical communication ensures that there are co-operation and understanding among people in the organisation. Horizontal communication is as important except one should see it more than a working ethic along. Communicating with your partners in work help you works better as a team. But, at the same time, you should also bear in mind that it is an opportunity for you to build your relationship with your peer.</p><p>In business, communication is very important. It plays a role in helping everyone in the organisation co-operate with each other and connect with customers and other partnered organisations as well. One who work in business need to have good communication skills in both oral and written. At all time, their communication must be formal and professional. Not only should you talk to deliver information and send feedback, you must also speak up in a way that other listen and empathize with you. But at the same time, you must be able to listen with what other have to say as well to maintain a balance two-ways communication.</p><p>We must keep in mind that in business, communication will determine how successful you are in the workplace.</p><p>Source: Cambridge IGCSE Business Studies Textbook 2nd Edition)</p><h3 id="How-it-affect-motivation"><a href="#How-it-affect-motivation" class="headerlink" title="How it affect motivation?"></a>How it affect motivation?</h3><p>Giving you a detailed view on the matter.</p><p>How does communication affect motivation?<br>Before discussing this topic, I would like you to watch this very motivational speech made by Steve Job, the founder of Apple Inc at Stanford University on 12 June, 2006. See for yourself how he brought motivation upon the many students of Stanford as well as many who have watched this video and you.  </p><p>If you have watch the full video, I believe you felt enlightened and motivated by this speech yourself. Motivational speaker such as Steve Job or Barack Obama are not rare at all. In fact, you probably know such people from your daily life experience as well. These motivational speakers have a great way to get others inspired. They are able to attract the attention of others and turn everything they said into an empowerment to the listeners. But, why do people like Steve Jobs want to motivates people?</p><p>In business, knowing how to communicate effectively in order to inspire the employees is a job that many managers are trying to achieve. The reason is simple: motivation eventually lead to more productivity. Motivation in workplace is often triggered when the managers find his way of speaking to his employee. Effective communication by the managers will result in changing the mood within the co-operate and inspire employees to work harder towards common goals. Not only so, a motivated group of people tend to have more co-operation among each other, which will result in more encouraged better teamwork and better outcomes. On the other hand, an article on Love2Reward said that 91% of companies with internal communication problems tend to find motivation at low level.</p><p>Motivation at workplace heavily depends on how the manager influence his workers. It is for a fact that employee feel more enthusiastic to work when they have a proactive leader who pay attentions to the workers. Manager who try to communicate effective by being friendly instead of trying to be the boss often win the employee over easier. This will not only make sure that communication will be channel effectively as the emotional barrier is eliminate and the managers and employee build a stronger bond. When employee feel that their boss is friendly and pay respect them, they will feel more comfortable and motivated to work.</p><p>All it takes for a leader to deliver a motivational speech is to be confidence. As you have observed from the Steve Job speech video, you could see that he comfortably spoke in front of many people. He spoke with a very calm tone and a lot of emotion expression it it. He even make jokes like at 04:40 where he said Microsoft copied Apple. Then, as he continued with his stories, he delivered some inspirational messages such as “you gotta ind what you love to do” (8:24) or “keep looking, don’t settle” (8:39). At the end of the video, you could see how many Stanford graduate has become as they clapped and cheer for him. Being motivational speaker is not difficult at all. It just require good, persuasive communication skills and confidence to speak out the message. When the message is delivered successfully, people are inspired and motivated.</p><p>In conclusion, motivation comes from a positive environment in the workplace and communication can do so. By channeling communication effectively within the organisation, managers and employee are not being shunned by the communication barriers such as emotion or structural problem, thus, lead to stronger bonds and co-operation. This will allow manager to interact more with their employees and be attentive to them. As this happen, employees will feel respected by their manager and felt more motivated to do work. In addition, managers who want to motivate their employee have to have confidence. They must be able to communicate to their employee with confidence and comfort, creating a close feeling between him and his employees while also draw out important inspirational messages. In today’s world, professionalism is very important in workplace, but ensure that workers are motivated to work is much more important as it will create the desire to aim for success and result in higher productivity and outcomes. That’s why communication should be practice effectively.  </p><p><img src="https://maxcommunicationmotivation.weebly.com/uploads/1/5/6/8/15680400/854441.jpg?466" alt=""><br>Let’s aim toward a motivated working environment !</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/7844471_orig.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equality and respect, seeking common ground while reserving differences, cooperation and win-win, flexible response, and getting things done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Communication" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Communication/"/>
    
      <category term="Cooperation" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Cooperation/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Habit</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Habit.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Habit.html</id>
    <published>2018-09-08T02:11:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-09-08T02:21:35.839Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/habit-loop.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Good habits make life.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/GoodHabitsBadHabits_1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>It is the same thing that has led to your success and failure.</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/image-1024x613.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Habitloop.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/habit-loop.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Good habits make life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Habit" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Habit/"/>
    
      <category term="Circle" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Circle/"/>
    
      <category term="Practice" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Practice/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Black Hole</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Black-Hole.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Black-Hole.html</id>
    <published>2018-09-08T01:57:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-09-08T02:38:45.374Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/star_black_hole.webp?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Inferiority and jealousy, bad habits, vicious circle are all black holes in energy.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p>Control your attention through meditation and build full confidence through self-discipline and growth.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/how-to-deal-with-jealousy-by-the-skinny-confidential-1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>it’s better to go back and make a net than to stand by the pond and long for fish</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/ViciousCircleOfNegativeThoughts.JPG?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Vicious circle of negative thoughts</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/jealousy.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p>Using Jealousy as a Manifesting Tool<br>When this concept of jealousy was shared with me it was a paradigm shift.<br>You mean I can use what I was beating myself up about,<br>as a tool to help guide me towards what I DO WANT?<br>Hold the phone!<br>Don’t take away my vicitimhood.<br>I need something to beat myself up about…. ahhhhh..<br>(said the old Lisa)<br>It’s your choice.<br>You can continue to see jealousy as something that takes you down, triggering you into feeling bad about yourself and charging what you don’t have in life.<br>OR<br>You can use this energy as a tool.—–</p><blockquote><p>“You are the average of the five people you spend the most time with.” – Jim Rohn</p></blockquote><p>When I heard this quote, I started going where people had what I wanted and my frequency started to shift. I wanted to make more money, so I hung out with people who had money. I wanted to travel more, so I would hang out at hotels where people were traveling. I wanted to do more art, so I would go to gallery openings. Where your energy goes your life flows, it doesn’t matter if someone else has it, to me that is just proof that it’s possible.</p><p>Inquire Within Exercise:</p><ol><li>What is something that triggers jealousy in you? When someone has <strong>____</strong> I get jealous.</li><li>Describe the kind of person you want to be?</li><li>Who are the 5 people you spend the most time with?</li><li>Do these people embody the qualities you are seeking for yourself?</li><li>What is one thing you can do to move you closer to being what you described in number 2?</li></ol><p>youcandoit!</p><p>If you want support in making changes in your life, sign up for a FREE VISION CALL and we can talk about how awesome you are. 🙂</p><p><a href="https://www.theskinnyconfidential.com/jealousy-waste-energy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"></a>. It doesn’t help you. It doesn’t help your relationship. It’s not going to stop anything; as a matter of fact it will probably only make something happen. Men are like children in some respects. When we were kids and our parents or teachers told us not to do something, it only made us want to do it more. The best thing you can do in a relationship is give the other person freedom. This is for two reasons: first, if someone wants to step out on you they are going to step out and there is nothing you can do. Better to find out early and be done. Second, men are attracted to confidence ( at least men worth being with ) &amp; there is nothing more attractive than a confident woman who is confident in the relationship. It’s no fun being in a relationship and listening to insecurities. BIG turn off. With Lauryn, she is not the jealous type. I have never been tempted to step out or cheat. A lot of that has to do with me and integrity…but a big part is her attitude. <strong>She doesn’t care if I go out with friends, she’s not looking through my phone or e-mails. She just trusts me and in turn, that makes me trust her. She’s too busy to be wasting time on worry &amp; jealousy. I like that.</strong></p><h2 id="A-VICIOUS-CIRCLE"><a href="#A-VICIOUS-CIRCLE" class="headerlink" title="A VICIOUS CIRCLE"></a><a href="https://trainingmag.com/trgmag-article/vicious-circle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">A VICIOUS CIRCLE</a></h2><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/lastwordStressRudenesscircle.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p>By curbing the inclination to act impulsively, you can improve relationships and avoid entering the stress/rudeness vicious circle.</p><p>Article Author:<br>By Peter Post, Director, The Emily Post Institute<br>What happens to cause people to act in a rude manner? Possible moments when rudeness can rear its ugly head include:</p><p>When disagreement occurs. A discussion in which people don’t agree turns personal rather than remains focused on the issue.<br>When time pressure builds at work. The deadline for a column causes the author to be curt with others as he attempts to turn it in on time.<br>When people are asked to do more with less. Downsizing is tough on those let go, but it also places additional demands on those still on the job and leaves them wondering if they might be next.<br>When technology builds an electronic brick wall between people. A person receives a less-than-friendly e-mail and rather than taking the time to cool down first, fires off an angry response, starting a chain of angry e-mails.<br>If you had a blood pressure cuff on people at the time these situations happened, you’d see their readings increase— sometimes dramatically. In each case, it’s easy to imagine the stress level in the office or between the people involved sky-rocketing. Unfortunately, the resultant stress increases the odds for rudeness to occur, and that can lead to the stress/rudeness vicious circle.</p><p>The vicious circle begins when stress increases between people. As it increases, it leads to loss of awareness as the stressed person becomes more focused on him- or herself and not on how his or her actions are affecting others. In turn, that loss of awareness leads to actions that, at the very least, appear rude. The rudeness, in turn, ramps up the stress the affected people feel. And now all parties are ensnared in the stress/rudeness vicious circle.</p><p>Another stress factor is introduced when people act impulsively, doing the first thing that comes to mind without thinking about the consequences. For instance, Tom and Andy are having a conversation and Tom’s cell phone rings. Without thinking about the effect on Andy, Tom answers his phone, leaving Andy to think Tom is pretty rude. So Andy throws his hands up in disgust and walks away. Tom perceives Andy’s action as rude and way over the top and, suddenly, they became trapped in the stress/ rudeness vicious circle, all because of two impulsive actions: Tom answering his phone and Andy’s impulsive response to Tom’s action.</p><p>Had Tom stayed his hand for just a few seconds while his phone was ringing and focused on how answering it might be perceived by Andy, he might have chosen to send the call to voicemail. Andy would have noticed the action and instead of being frustrated with Tom, he would have appreciated the non-verbal signal that Tom considered their conversation to be more important than a phone call from who knows who.</p><p>By curbing the inclination to act impulsively, you can improve relationships and avoid entering the stress/rudeness vicious circle.</p><h2 id="3-Biblical-Truths-About-Envy-And-Jealousy"><a href="#3-Biblical-Truths-About-Envy-And-Jealousy" class="headerlink" title="3 Biblical Truths About Envy And Jealousy"></a><a href="https://theprayingwoman.com/3-biblical-truths-about-envy-and-jealousy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">3 Biblical Truths About Envy And Jealousy</a></h2><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/jealousy20180908.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><ol><li>Jealousy can lead to your downfall.<br>For where jealousy and selfish ambition exist, there will be disorder and every vile practice. – James 3:16</li></ol><p>“Oh, did you see … and …?” “Look at her, girl I’d love to have her… ”</p><p>Jealousy. In the bible, we see that Saul was jealous of David, but to note, Saul brought his troubles upon himself.</p><p>A tool created by the devil. Jealousy will cause people to act strange and even harm people to the point of death.</p><p>What those who have this spirit upon them fail to realize is that they have their own set of gifts and blessings that God has given them, so why envy someone else and their blessing?</p><p>Also, some people with this spirit feel threatened by someone who appears to be higher than them; notice I said appear.</p><p>Just because the gift may be wrapped with the finest wrapping paper and most beautiful bow, what it holds inside may be rotten to the core.</p><p>Jealous people often times feel insecure, powerless, and doubt themselves about getting what they are jealous about.</p><ol start="2"><li>Jealousy is more detrimental than wrath or anger.<br>Wrath is cruel, anger is overwhelming, but who can stand before jealousy? – Proverbs 27:4</li></ol><p>The spirit of jealousy is very detrimental among women, especially Christian woman.</p><p>Why can’t we just be happy and celebrate when our sister gets her blessing she’s been waiting/praying on, instead of eyeing her and making her uncomfortable because of the worldly way we may accuse of her getting her blessing.</p><p>If you have this spirit upon you, you may question or 2nd guess yourself and your abilities, again forgetting that what God has for you is for you along with YOUR OWN set of blessings.</p><p>Jealousy is of the flesh, and fleshy desires/acts never work out for the good of God.</p><p>Jealousy can have you so caught up that it could destroy your life, because you’re too busy noticing what she has while you could be losing everything.</p><p>When you recognize this spirit in your presence, remember you have the power of the Holy Spirit within you to overcome it; Call it out.</p><p>Move forward in Faith and ask for the covering of the Blood of Jesus. Remove yourself from that spirit and pray for that Sister.</p><p>Ask God to open her eyes so she can see her own blessings.</p><p>Show your Godly wisdom and discipline</p><p>If you feel you have this spirit upon you, STOP and REPENT!! Ask the Holy Spirit to come in and bind that spirit, so you can see your own blessings God has for you and has provided for you.</p><p>Submit to God. Have Faith and read the Word of God in the Bible. Once you are equipped with the armor of God, the attacks and spirits of jealousy will have a hard time entering your atmosphere.</p><ol start="3"><li>When you are content, you don’t have to be jealous.<br>Not that I am speaking of being in need, for I have learned in whatever situation I am to be content. 12 I know how to be brought low, and I know how to abound. In any and every circumstance, I have learned the secret of facing plenty and hunger, abundance and need.  – Philippians 4:11-12</li></ol><p>Be content in everything God has provided for YOU! You have your own set of blessings!!</p><p>Sometimes we’re so busy counting everyone else’s blessings that we forget to count our own.</p><p>Keep your eyes on your prize! Jesus Christ!</p><h2 id="5-Symptoms-of-Inferiority-Complex-And-5-Ways-How-To-Overcome-It"><a href="#5-Symptoms-of-Inferiority-Complex-And-5-Ways-How-To-Overcome-It" class="headerlink" title="5 Symptoms of Inferiority Complex And 5 Ways How To Overcome It"></a><a href="https://www.lifecoachcode.com/2018/01/24/inferiority-complex-5-ways-how-to-overcome-it/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">5 Symptoms of Inferiority Complex And 5 Ways How To Overcome It</a></h2><p>January 24, 2018</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Big-fish-small-pond-shutterstock_8451121.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p>Having a down feeling after a major life setback or failure in some kind of endeavor is normal. These failures might make you feel worthless or useless.</p><p>After wallowing on your pain for a day or two, you should feel better to face another day. However, if the feelings of worthlessness is long overdue and is getting worse with the passing of days, it might indicate that you’re having an inferiority complex.</p><p>Inferiority complex prevents you from seeing your true worth and focus only on your flaws. It gives you a thousand reasons why you can’t do a thing rightly and why others perform better than you.</p><p>People having an inferiority complex think only of their weaknesses and see every situation through this lens.</p><p>Some root causes of an inferiority complex can also be traced through childhood experiences that leave a permanent dent in a child’s psyche. This child will grow up having self-doubt and feeling not good enough compared to other people.</p><p>Identifying the symptoms of an inferiority complex is the first step in overcoming it. Here are some of them and the ways to face them.</p><p>Symptoms of Inferiority Complex:</p><ol><li>You often have feelings of worthlessness.<br>Feelings of worthlessness commonly arise when you keep comparing yourself with others. You have this fixed notion that everyone you see has a better life, better qualities, and better skills than you are.</li></ol><p>You see others as entities who could never go wrong nor can have any bad days.</p><ol start="2"><li>You are overly sensitive to criticisms.<br>You react quickly every time you receive criticisms. Even the most constructive ones make you shrink and doubt your abilities.</li></ol><p>Because criticisms make you vulnerable, you choose not to say a word or do a thing.</p><ol start="3"><li>You have a preconceived idea that people don’t like you.<br>Even if you’re not sure what others are thinking, you imagine that others don’t like you. Or, if you’re about to meet people, you believe that they would have a negative judgment about you the moment they see you or come to know you.</li></ol><p>Thinking this way, you will behave in a way that others don’t approve of. Eventually, you repel others from liking you.</p><ol start="4"><li>You are submissive.<br>Because you don’t feel you’re good enough, you don’t have the strength to stand for yourself. You’re submissive to the whims of others to the point of being abused by them.</li></ol><p>Instead of finding your own voice, you settle for it as if it’s the lot life gives you.</p><ol start="5"><li>You are a perfectionist.<br>You believe that everything you do has to be perfect. Whenever you fail to do something perfectly, you see it as utter failure.</li></ol><p>Everything has to be flawless and must pass the high standards you have set upon.</p><p>Like any other personality problems, you can overcome inferiority complex by doing the inner work that helps you heal.</p><p>How To Overcome Inferiority Complex:Inferiority Complex 5 Ways How To Overcome It</p><p><img src="https://www.lifecoachcode.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/5-Symptoms-of-Inferiority-Complex-And-5-Ways-How-To-Overcome-It.jpg" alt=""></p><ol><li>Get inspiration from others instead of wanting to be like them.</li></ol><p>People are normal human beings who share the same traits as you. They also have pains, have soft spots, have rough edges, or might have been going through difficult times.</p><p>When you come to understand people, you will come to understand yourself.</p><p>Know the stories of great men and women. Their stories will give you light that you are more than what you think and your worth is more than you could ever imagine.</p><ol start="2"><li>Use criticism to your best advantage.</li></ol><p>Whether given in a positive or negative manner, you can use criticisms to your best advantage. See criticisms as a gauge of improving yourself and not a way to put you down.</p><p>Criticisms are hints that point you to the aspects of yourself that needs improvement.</p><ol start="3"><li>Be yourself and build self-confidence.</li></ol><p>Be the self that you want to be not the self that you think others might dislike. Begin by accepting yourself as you are.</p><p>By self-acceptance, you are giving others the reason to accept yourself too. Think and act in a manner that builds your confidence.</p><ol start="4"><li>Develop your own voice.</li></ol><p>Realize that you weren’t born to be a doormat other people have to step on. Find the inner strength and work on it until you’re able to stand on your own and defend yourself.</p><p>Stop your negative self-talk and start with the positive ones.</p><ol start="5"><li>Practice self help therapy.</li></ol><p>While seeking professional help is a common solution for perfectionism, self help therapy works equally good, as long as you’re determined enough to get the best out of it.</p><p>You can heal yourself by journaling, having self discipline, self monitoring, and being honest with yourself.</p><p>Keep in mind that you’re not sent into this world to be perfect; but to be happy, to live your best life, and make the small corner of your world a much better place because you’re a part of it.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/star_black_hole.webp?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Inferiority and jealousy, bad habits, vicious circle are all black holes in energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Wisdom/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Hole" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Hole/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Elephant</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Elephant.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Elephant.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-31T12:02:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-31T12:03:22.224Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/elephant20180808.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Elephant – Roll up, Throw up, Tread.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/elephant20180808.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elephant – Roll up, Throw up, Tread.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Wisdom/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Elephant" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Elephant/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>PNPR</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/PNPR.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/PNPR.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-31T11:49:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-31T11:57:05.918Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/benjaminfranklin1-2x.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Preview, Note, Practice, Review</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Preview"><a href="#Preview" class="headerlink" title="Preview"></a>Preview</h2><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/R1861-WM__86030.1488573801.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Never fight a war without preparation. Opportunities are reserved for those who are prepared.</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/suntzu1-2x.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p>War chess deduction</p><h2 id="Note"><a href="#Note" class="headerlink" title="Note"></a>Note</h2><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/bigstock-Losing-memory-alzheimers-dementia-or-8040209-1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>A good memory is worse than a bad pen.</p></blockquote><h2 id="Practice"><a href="#Practice" class="headerlink" title="Practice"></a>Practice</h2><blockquote><p>The most fundamental Learning and creation: practice.</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/practicemakesperfect.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""><br>Practice makes perfect.<br>Practice makes progress.<br>The more you pratice, the better you get.</p><p>Every day to grow, every day to progress-this is my job.</p><p>When you think of it, you do it the right way-whether others understand it or not-that’s practice.</p><p><img src="http://zhibimo.com/read/xiaolai/reborn-every-7-years/images/A02-1.jpg" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Obviously, my approach is cost-effective. When I had already crossed 20 scales on the timeline, others were still within 13.7, and many more might not have crossed five. Compound interest effect is more obvious in my body, this is obviously very natural ah.</p></blockquote><p>To see the compound effect, you must have a long enough time, and the more significant the effect.</p><p> Time is not manageable, so you can only find ways to improve your work efficiency and quality of life.</p><p>When you think about it, you learn it, you take it seriously; when you do it, and that’s practice.</p><p>Everyone is born, can only be original. As a result, the vast majority of people who live accidentally turn themselves into pirates.</p><p>There are many reasonable people, but few practice them.</p><p>The money spent, just belong to yourself, time treasured, can count into the life, this is the simple truth.</p><p>Every day, I am very happy, very good very strong, more and more calm. Who knows about tomorrow-I know it myself.</p><p>Perform basic exercises, such as bathing and mouthwash, meditating walking, etc.</p><h2 id="Review"><a href="#Review" class="headerlink" title="Review"></a>Review</h2><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/timeforeviews-2000x1200.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Learn from the past. Consider the past you shall know the future</p></blockquote><p>Preview, notes and review are a complete set of learning methodologies.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/1967655-Thomas-S-Monson-Quote-Learn-from-the-past-prepare-for-the-future.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/mother20180811.JPG?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Review from Failure and Learn from it .</p></blockquote><p>Actively embrace change and failure,<br>Learn and grow for life.</p><p>One of the root causes of failure—too…</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/17751-Joyce-Meyer-Quote-Patience-is-not-the-ability-to-wait-but-the.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>A sudden realization is a moment, but a change takes time.</p></blockquote><p>A chance is easy, but it is hard to hold on for a long time.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/thomasedison20180811.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>You’ll never be brave if you don’t get hurt.<br>You’ll never be learn if you don’t make mistake.<br>You’ll never be successful if you don’t encounter failure.</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/johnroberts20180812001.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p>It is worth trying to think why that is so. And when you do, I think you may appreciate that it was because of the support of your classmates in the classroom, on the athletic field and in the dorms. And as far as the confidence goes, I think you will appreciate that it is not because you succeeded at everything you did, but because <strong>with the help of your friends, you were not afraid to fail</strong>. And if you did fail, you got up and tried again. And if you failed again, you got up and tried again. And if you failed again, it might be time to think about doing something else. <strong>But it was not just success, but not being afraid to fail that brought you to this point.</strong></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/causes-of-irritability.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Too eager to prove oneself</p></blockquote><p>Be eager to succeed<br>Lack of patience</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/atardecer-y-estrellas-en-el-teide-con-teleferico.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Life experience is the best teacher</p></blockquote><p>Lack of experience,<br>Cognitive errors</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/reading1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Lack of knowledge and skills</p></blockquote><p>Lack of energy<br>Lack of economic base<br>Family disharmony</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/7215ca8f7cbcfe135059d96bf2869638_interpersonal-relationship-intimate-relationship-download-clip-art-relationship-clipart-png_900-680.jpeg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Neglect of interpersonal relationships</p></blockquote><p>The essence of interpersonal relationship is:</p><ol><li>to grow together</li><li>cooperate and win together.</li></ol><p>Failure is not terrible. The real horror is that you<a href="http://zhibimo.com/read/xiaolai/reborn-every-7-years/A05.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> almost succeeded</a>.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/benjaminfranklin1-2x.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preview, Note, Practice, Review&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Review" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Review/"/>
    
      <category term="Practice" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Practice/"/>
    
      <category term="Preview" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Preview/"/>
    
      <category term="Note" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Note/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Funnel</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Funnel.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Funnel.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-31T05:24:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-31T09:21:22.015Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/1_VacFfCMOrP2CNX_Byoy3QQ.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Block the funnel to accumulate, such as study, profession, energy and connections…</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p>Energy–</p><ol><li>Meditation–Attention</li><li>Sleep        – Refresh</li><li>Music       – Light music</li><li>Movie      – Entertainment</li><li>Movement</li><li>Travel</li><li>Reading</li><li>Communication</li><li>Share</li><li>Play</li></ol><p>It’s the same people and things that affect attention, and the best strategy is to be inclusive, to let go, to be together and to be grateful, and to focus on your own growth and goals.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/rogers-marketing-funnel1.gif?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/slide_4.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/6aa92b228a5ccbd90b962855ac2bc560d0c2c80f.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/marketing-funnel-diagram-old-new.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/1_VacFfCMOrP2CNX_Byoy3QQ.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Block the funnel to accumulate, such as study, profession, energy and connections…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Funnel" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Funnel/"/>
    
      <category term="Hopper" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Hopper/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Period</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Period.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Period.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-31T02:50:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-31T02:50:24.955Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/economic-cycle.webp?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Spiral rise.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/china_uk_growth.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/static1.squarespace.com.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p>Work hard, go down again, run out three times</p><p>Too much effort often backfires.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Amplified_sine_wave.svg.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Sine Wave</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/sleep-stages-and-brain-activity-8-hour-sleep-cycle.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt="sleep-stages-and-brain-activity-8-hour-sleep-cycle.jpg"></p><blockquote><p>Sleep Period</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/1a4fa-sleep-cycle.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p><a href="https://cupidnpsyche.wordpress.com/2015/01/26/sleep-cycle/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Sleep Cycle</a></p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/p8242327.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Up</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/a-286-steep-going-down.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Down</p></blockquote>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/economic-cycle.webp?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spiral rise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Wisdom/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Rhythm" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Rhythm/"/>
    
      <category term="Period" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Period/"/>
    
      <category term="Cycle" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Cycle/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Price</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Price.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Price.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-31T02:22:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-31T11:33:54.960Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/pricecostandvalue.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Exchange costs a price, and only you can judge the value.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/no-pain-no-gain-1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Big pay, big gain,<br> little pay, little gain,<br> no pain, no gain.</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Live-Life-Love-8x10-1.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Life is dear, love is dearer, both are disposable if you are free.</p></blockquote>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/pricecostandvalue.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exchange costs a price, and only you can judge the value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Wisdom/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Price" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Price/"/>
    
      <category term="Cost" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Cost/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>QA</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/QA.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/QA.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-30T12:45:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-31T11:45:48.726Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/questions-and-answers.jpeg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Find the root causes and solutions by asking questions.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/5Whys_multiple_lanes_v3.webp?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>5Whys</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Steps-to-Success-628x353.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Success is the father of success.</p></blockquote><p>Question: Why can you succeed?</p><blockquote><p>Answer: Because of my choice and practice  – Minority, Correct and Value</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/ready20180811.gif?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Opportunities are reserved for those who are prepared.</p></blockquote>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/questions-and-answers.jpeg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find the root causes and solutions by asking questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Question" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Question/"/>
    
      <category term="Answer" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Answer/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Try</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Try.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Try.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-30T12:29:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-30T12:33:25.109Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/slide_35.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Try it. Nothing is impossible. It is often presumptuous ideas that stand in your way.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/1596013-Thomas-Heywood-Quote-Nothing-is-impossible-to-the-willing-heart.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/slide_35.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Try it. Nothing is impossible. It is often presumptuous ideas that stand in your way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Try" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Try/"/>
    
      <category term="Trial" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Trial/"/>
    
      <category term="Attempt" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Attempt/"/>
    
      <category term="Experiment" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Experiment/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>GPAR</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/GPAR.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/GPAR.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-28T08:08:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-28T08:16:14.962Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/goal-plan-action-success-sketch-46904431.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>GPA+Review</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/d-business-action-plan-checklist-illustration-check-mark-selected-option-vision-mission-goals-31279778.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/performance-planning-management-handbook-46-638.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Commitment-Timeline_Climate_Orange.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/goal-plan-action-success-sketch-46904431.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GPA+Review&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Goal" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Goal/"/>
    
      <category term="Plan" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Plan/"/>
    
      <category term="Action" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Action/"/>
    
      <category term="Review" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Review/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>ORID</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/ORID.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/ORID.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-28T02:17:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-28T02:22:31.526Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/ORID_+Focused+Conversation+Data+Analysis.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Object, Reflection, Interpretive, Decision</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/orid-template-copy-1-638.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Orid Template</p></blockquote>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/ORID_+Focused+Conversation+Data+Analysis.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Object, Reflection, Interpretive, Decision&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Decision" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Decision/"/>
    
      <category term="Object" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Object/"/>
    
      <category term="Reflection" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Reflection/"/>
    
      <category term="Interpretive" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Interpretive/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Break Down</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Break-Down.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Break-Down.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-27T00:14:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-31T11:59:06.282Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Ob6bKZiLiVAWJMAg.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Break up the whole into pieces and destroy them one by one</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><a href="http://www.luojiji.com/thread-10050-1-1.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"></a> is the ability to break a big goal down into a bunch of small goals and do it right away.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/everythingbeefflat-careful-division.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Dismember an ox as skillfully as a butcher</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/1207657700-1_u_1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Reading dismantling</p></blockquote>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Ob6bKZiLiVAWJMAg.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Break up the whole into pieces and destroy them one by one&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Disassembly" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Disassembly/"/>
    
      <category term="Decompose" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Decompose/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Observer</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Observer.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Observer.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-26T23:14:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-26T23:18:23.139Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/obServer.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>The spectators see the chess game better than the players.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p>Look away from different perspectives</p><p><img src="http://7xvdkv.com1.z0.glb.clouddn.com/image/design_pattern/obServerClassicUML.jpg" alt=""><br>publish/subscribe</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/obServer.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The spectators see the chess game better than the players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Wisdom/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Wisdom/"/>
    
      <category term="Observer" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Observer/"/>
    
      <category term="Viewpoint" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Viewpoint/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Convergence Trend</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Convergence-Trend.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Convergence-Trend.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-26T22:48:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-30T09:43:10.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/ijerph-13-00620-g008.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Convergence, Focus, Evolution.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p>The reason for convergence is because resources are limited.</p><p>Such as:</p><p>Read a book<br>Write a report<br>Take 10,000 steps a day<br>Meditate for 30 minutes every day<br>…</p><p>Complementing the <a href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Compound-Interest.html">compound interest</a> effect</p><p>Profession<br>Debt<br>Information<br>Game<br>Entertainment</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/ijerph-13-00620-g008.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Convergence, Focus, Evolution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Wisdom/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Convergence" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Convergence/"/>
    
      <category term="Trend" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Trend/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>WOOP</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/WOOP.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/WOOP.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-25T08:16:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-25T22:49:05.220Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/woopjpeg004export1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> Wish–&gt;Outcome–&gt;Obstacle–&gt;Plan</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/woopjpegsample20061-1024x837.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/woopjpeg004export1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Wish–&amp;gt;Outcome–&amp;gt;Obstacle–&amp;gt;Plan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Plan" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Plan/"/>
    
      <category term="Wish" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Wish/"/>
    
      <category term="Outcome" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Outcome/"/>
    
      <category term="Obstacle" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Obstacle/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>IPO</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/IPO.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/IPO.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-23T08:07:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-23T08:16:39.348Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Marketing-technology-input-process-output-2.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p> All activities fall into these three categories. – Input, Process, Output.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p>Intermediate nodes that have no output are useless nodes.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/slide_2.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Every node takes a lot of effort.</p></blockquote><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/08ffa006b0a92966bca30b3731a51fd1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Food+Processor+Hospital+Process+Inputs+Processing+Outputs.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/input-output-process-storage-cycle.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Inputs+Processes+Outputs+Information+Systems+Planning+Process.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Marketing-technology-input-process-output-2.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt; All activities fall into these three categories. – Input, Process, Output.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Input" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Input/"/>
    
      <category term="Process" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Process/"/>
    
      <category term="Output" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Output/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Patience</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Patience.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Profession/Patience.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-23T03:13:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-23T03:17:03.614Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Patience-is-a-Virtue-1024x585.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Be friends with time.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p>Patience is the core of wisdom.</p><p>The law of the development of things - from quantitative to qualitative.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/A-moment-of-patience1.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/2286-Bill-Gates-Quote-Patience-is-a-key-element-of-success.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Patience-is-a-Virtue-1024x585.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be friends with time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Profession" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Profession/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Patience" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Patience/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Damocles</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Damocles.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Damocles.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-22T23:24:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-22T23:31:29.788Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Damocles-WestallPC20080120-8842A.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>People without thought, he must worry about.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><p>If you say that someone has the Sword of Damocles hanging over their head, you mean that they are in a situation in which something very bad could happen to them at any time.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/Damocles-WestallPC20080120-8842A.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People without thought, he must worry about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Wisdom/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Damocles" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Damocles/"/>
    
      <category term="Model" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Model/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Pyramid</title>
    <link href="http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Pyramid.html"/>
    <id>http://ideeplearn.com/Wisdom/Pyramid.html</id>
    <published>2018-08-22T23:11:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2018-08-22T23:23:20.207Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/PyramidModellogo_nobackground.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><blockquote><p>Step by step, step by layer.</p></blockquote><a id="more"></a><h2 id="Maslow-Pyramid"><a href="#Maslow-Pyramid" class="headerlink" title="Maslow Pyramid"></a>Maslow Pyramid</h2><p>Upper decision decided by the economic background.</p><p>The horses are weak because they are thin, and people are not motivated because of poverty.</p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/maslow-5.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/1_WjUwZeUTJvzYqFN0-ytpjg.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p><p><img src="http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/maslow3.jpg?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p" alt=""></p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pd4vb8220.bkt.clouddn.com/PyramidModellogo_nobackground.png?imageMogr2/thumbnail/!75p&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step by step, step by layer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="Wisdom" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/categories/Wisdom/"/>
    
    
      <category term="Model" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Model/"/>
    
      <category term="Pyramid" scheme="http://ideeplearn.com/tags/Pyramid/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
